<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Precision Analytics</title>
    <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Precision Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 Precision Analytics.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring your dog to blog day</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/4rover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/4rover/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Kathryn   If you know me, you know that I really, really like dogs. To fulfill the dog-shaped hole currently in my heart, I’ve been dog-sitting on Rover for the last year1. I get paid to hang out with dogs! Before you quit your job, I get $28/day and spend half on treats and toys. But, I absolutely love it. If you don’t mind planning your day around a dog, I couldn’t recommend it more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The most helpful (and shaming) productivity tool ever</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/30/3rescue-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/30/3rescue-time/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Erika  
During my studies, I struggled to evaluate my productivity. The research years of my PhD were long and lacked structure. It felt as though I spent every day sitting in front of my computer slowly chipping away at the amorphous blob that was my thesis. I discovered Rescue Time and it totally changed my life! It&amp;rsquo;s an app that you can run on your desktop that tracks which ever active window your working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;having an office&#39; effect on cafe expenses</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/17/2office-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/17/2office-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Kathryn  
Precision Analytics found a permament home in July 2017 at Nexus Coworking space. Before then, we were working out of our own homes or at coffee shops.
I track my personal spending, and I noticed a pretty strong &amp;lsquo;office effect&amp;rsquo; on having a permanent space to work - and make my own coffee! The y-axis is proportionate to the dollars I spent at cafes per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our website is live!</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/06/26/1website-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/06/26/1website-live/</guid>
      <description>We built our website using Hugo and GitHub pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help Please feel free to get in touch for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/faq/</guid>
      <description>Who are your clients? Our clients include small business from pharmacoepidemiology and biotechnology sectors, as well as many individual clinicians, scientists, academics, and trainees. We have clients from across Canada, the US, and Europe.

Where are you located? Our office is located in the Montreal Quebec, in the Plateau, at 4529 Rue Clark.

Can you help me with my scientific report, manuscript, or thesis? Absolutely, we offer guidance at every stage of empirical research, from protocol development, sample size/power calculations, study design, analysis, interpretation, and publication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Services</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/services/</guid>
      <description>We offer a range of services from analytics to research support. We’ve worked with clients from the private and public sector, including academics, professionals, graduate students, corporations and start-ups. 
Statistical consulting Maximize the quality and amount of information you get from your data. Whether you use SAS, R, SPSS, Stata, SQL, our team has the technical know-how to assist in all stages of your project. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know these tools, we can perform analyses for you (see data analysis) or help you improve your proficiency (see tutoring).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/team/</guid>
      <description>Erika Braithwaite, PhD | Co-Founder I obtained my bachelors and master’s in psychology and then completed a PhD in Epidemiology at McGill University. My journey from the social sciences to the biomedical field has helped me gain a host of expertise related to study design, such as clinical trials, statistical modeling techniques drawn from causal inference and econometrics. The common thread to all the fun things I get to do in my everyday?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terams of service</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/legal/</guid>
      <description>Precision Analytics Terms of Service  Terms By accessing the website at http://www.precision-analytics.ca, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>