<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Precision Analytics</title>
    <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Precision Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 Precision Analytics.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring your dog to blog day</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/4rover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/4rover/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Kathryn   If you know me, you know that I really, really like dogs. To fulfill the dog-shaped hole currently in my heart, I’ve been dog-sitting on Rover for the last year1. I get paid to hang out with dogs! Before you quit your job, I get $28/day and spend half on treats and toys. But, I absolutely love it. If you don’t mind planning your day around a dog, I couldn’t recommend it more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring your dog to blog day</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/5ssc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/10/06/5ssc/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Kathryn   Last month I received my accreditation an associate statistician from the Statistical Society of Canada (SSC).




 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The most helpful (and shaming) productivity tool ever</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/30/3rescue-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/30/3rescue-time/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Erika  
During my studies, I struggled to evaluate my productivity. The research years of my PhD were long and lacked structure. It felt as though I spent every day sitting in front of my computer slowly chipping away at the amorphous blob that was my thesis. I discovered Rescue Time and it totally changed my life! It&amp;rsquo;s an app that you can run on your desktop that tracks which ever active window your working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;having an office&#39; effect on cafe expenses</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/17/2office-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/08/17/2office-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Post written by Kathryn  
Precision Analytics found a permament home in July 2017 at Nexus Coworking space. Before then, we were working out of our own homes or at coffee shops.
I track my personal spending, and I noticed a pretty strong &amp;lsquo;office effect&amp;rsquo; on having a permanent space to work - and make my own coffee! The y-axis is proportionate to the dollars I spent at cafes per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our website is live!</title>
      <link>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/06/26/1website-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kathryntmorrison.github.io/pa/blog/2017/06/26/1website-live/</guid>
      <description>We built our website using Hugo and GitHub pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>